I went to Yumo painting and calligraphy shop
我去了玉墨书画店
to convey information to him.
向他传达信息。
Work with him.
和他一起工作。
And today,
还有今天，
we are both in cahoots
我们同谋
identified the two drug dealers.
确定了两名毒贩的身份。
The purpose is
目的是
to give it time
给它时间
pkt at the tea shop.
pkt在茶馆。
And also
并且
You mean I'm Plum Blossom Four?
你是说我是梅花四？
I am "Plum Blossom Si".
我是“梅花斯”。
Komandan Luo.
Komandan Luo.
Check it carefully.
仔细检查一下。
If you don't check, you're an asshole.
如果你不检查，你就是个混蛋。
Really anxious.
确实很着急。
sister,
姐姐，
you're not much better than Zhao An,
你比赵安好不了多少
your mind is narrow.
你的思想很狭隘。
Manager Luo,
Manager Luo,
what about this old road?
这条老路怎么样？
Keep hanging.
继续挂。
Hang him until he dies.
绞死他直到他死。
Section Chief Chen
陈科长
gun barge
枪驳船
own weight is around 1,100 grams,
自重约为1,100克，
after pouring it weighs approximately 1350 grams
倒出后重量约为1350克
the weight of that gun
那把枪的重量
about 1,200 grams.
约1,200克。
Not a full weapon
不是完整的武器
nor is it an empty weapon
它也不是空的武器
there is one possibility
有一种可能性
already fired several bullets,
已经发射了几颗子弹
but it looks like the gun has a problem
但枪好像有问题
So
所以
is not firing a few bullets
不是发射几颗子弹
but the magazine contains empty bullets.
但弹匣里有空子弹。
You still have to figure out how to get to the bookstore.
你还得弄清楚怎么去书店。
Good.
好的。
Room upstairs.
楼上的房间。
In the middle of the floor, seventh floor.
第七层，中间一层。
I saved some papers and documents.
我保存了一些文件和文件。
You choose what is worthless.
你选择的是没有价值的东西。
Give it to Luo Guanqun.
交给罗冠群。
The rest must be thrown away.
其余的必须扔掉。
Good.
好的。
Second floor balcony.
二楼阳台。
I put a pot of yellow chrysanthemums,
我放了一盆黄菊花，
is a safe signal.
是一个安全信号。
You changed Huang Ju to Zi Ju,
You changed Huang Ju to Zi Ju,
indicates something has happened.
表明发生了某事。
And most importantly
最重要的是
4th brother plum blossom.
四弟梅花。
Be sure to investigate Shan's plans
一定要调查一下珊的计划
have to destroy it.
必须摧毁它。
Of course.
当然。
Enough already.
已经足够。
I've ordered
我已订购
everyone will die.
每个人都会死。
Die according to the desired state
根据想要的状态模具
deserve it
值得的
i...
我...
I'll think of a way
我会想办法
think of ways to please you.
想办法取悦你。
No need.
不需要。
I can hold it.
我能坚持住。
I hear
我听到
when people almost die
当人们快要死的时候
can see the person he most wants to see.
能够见到他最想见的人。
You can see the person you most want to see.
你可以见到你最想见的人。
If it's really like that,
如果真的是这样的话
I'm not afraid of how long the death process will be.
我并不害怕死亡的过程有多漫长。
Because there are those who accompany me.
因为还有陪伴我的人。
The old way
老办法
no matter where you end up.
无论你最终去往何处。
We will fight together
我们将一起战斗
fight together
一起战斗
Here
这里
addicted man
上瘾的人
Their sugar porridge and fried dumplings are the best.
他们的糖粥和煎饺是最好的。
Hurry up and try it.
赶快尝试一下吧。
Me
我
I'm a little hungry.
我有点饿了。
You two eat.
你们两个吃饭吧
How
如何
used to be every night after overtime
以前每天晚上加班后
I will come with my sister.
我会和姐姐一起来。
You still have a younger sibling.
你还有一个弟弟妹妹。
But he died before living for 18 years.
但他还没有活18年就去世了。
How did he die?
他怎么死的？
One night two years ago.
两年前的一个晚上。
He came to take me home.
他来接我回家。
I met a group of drunk Japanese soldiers,
我遇见了一群醉酒的日本兵，
then teased me.
然后取笑我。
Eat my tofu.
吃我的豆腐吧
My sister is young.
我姐姐还年轻。
Very angry,
很生气，
even looking for them to debate.
甚至找他们辩论。
They use punctures
他们使用穿刺
stabbed him in the stomach.
刺伤了他的肚子。
Case case
案例案例
selling sugar porridge.
卖糖粥。
3 kilograms jug, 4 kilograms shellfish.
3公斤水罐，4公斤贝类。
My little brother when he was little
我的弟弟小时候
I like reading this song the most.
我最喜欢读这首歌。
You must hate Japanese people, right?
你一定很讨厌日本人吧？
What's the point of hating?
恨有什么意义呢？
Can I beat them?
我能打败他们吗？
If one day you go to war,
如果有一天你去打仗，
are you willing to give your life for your sister?
你愿意为你的妹妹付出生命吗？
Kak Hong Ling.
嘉鸿凌.
Why are we walking this path?
我们为什么要走这条路？
Very dark.
很暗。
This road is close.
这条路很近。
Come in.
进来。
In front of my house.
在我家前面。
What dance are we learning today?
今天我们学什么舞蹈？
Today I will teach you
今天我就教你
The most popular Foxtrot dance in Shanghai, how about it?
上海最受欢迎的狐步舞，怎么样？
Tarian Foxtrot.
塔里安狐步舞。
Previously I had read a novel
之前看过一本小说
Foxtrot dance called Shanghai.
狐步舞叫上海。
The story is about a quiet little street.
故事讲述的是一条安静的小街道。
On a secluded little road.
在一条僻静的小路上。
It's terrible
它是可怕的
where there are so many murder cases
哪里有那么多谋杀案
but on this road there are often rats
但这条路上经常有老鼠
addicted man
上瘾的人
I'm most afraid of mice.
我最怕老鼠。
Can you walk in front of me?
你能走在我前面吗？
Then you follow me.
那你就跟着我吧。
Red.
红色的。
Big Brother Hong Ling.
鸿凌哥哥。
You...
你...
Why do you do like this?
你为什么要这样做？
Didn't think of it, right?
没想到吧？
I put medicine in your sugar porridge.
我在你的糖粥里放了药。
How
如何
kill him.
杀了他。
How to do it?
怎么做？
Like you said
像你说的
pass through the small road
穿过小路
shot him twice in the back.
从背后朝他开了两枪。
You didn't lie to me?
你没有骗我吧？
You should have heard the sound of the gun, right?
你应该听到枪声了吧？
But I heard gunshots a long time ago.
但我很久以前就听到了枪声。
Why are you only coming back now?
你怎么现在才回来？
Taking care of the corpse
照顾尸体
doesn't need time?
不需要时间？
Good.
好的。
Good work.
干得好。
Have you taken medicine?
你吃药了吗？
Already.
已经。
Has the bandage been changed?
绷带换了吗？
Not yet.
还没有。
I'll help you.
我会帮你。
Good.
好的。
Hong Ling.
洪凌.
Shi Yang was entrusted by the Chongqing military
石洋受重庆军方委托
had to lurk for a long time.
不得不潜伏很长一段时间。
He got important information
他得到了重要信息
but he didn't submit
但他没有提交
he ran away.
他逃跑了。
He threatened the headquarters to ransom the information for big money.
他威胁总部要以巨额赎金赎回这些信息。
What information did he get?
他得到了什么信息？
Japanese Army Ministry's plan to counterfeit French money.
日本陆军省计划伪造法国货币。
If you lose this information,
如果您丢失了这些信息，
Counterfeit French money will spread in this country
法国假币将在这个国家蔓延
the financial system will collapse
金融体系将会崩溃
war stuff gets worse
战争事情变得更糟
our victory is getting farther away.
我们的胜利已经越来越远了。
This is the price you deserve
这是你应得的价格
for your bright future.
为了您美好的未来。
I just don't want to kill innocent people.
我只是不想杀害无辜的人。
About what he did
关于他所做的事
I don't care
我不在乎
I don't care.
我不在乎。
Do you care?
你关心？
You and Shi Yang are not the same person,
你和石洋不是同一个人，
conscience?
良心？
Justice
正义
in your heart, nothing is destroyed.
在你的心里，没有什么被摧毁。
You will definitely help me
你一定会帮助我的
why steal my pendant
为什么要偷我的吊坠
I was wrong
我错了
I asked why you stole my locket
我问你为什么偷我的挂坠盒
that woman lied to me
那个女人对我撒谎
you didn't kill him.
你没有杀他。
Why don't you kill him?
你为什么不杀了他？
The woman told me
女人告诉我
if I give you your pendant
如果我给你你的吊坠
will share half the money you receive
将分享您收到的一半资金
I was wrong, I was really wrong.
我错了，我真的错了。
Rotten bitch.
烂婊子。
I I
二
turned out to trap me behind.
竟然把我困在了后面。
I am wrong.
我错了。
I have gambling debts,
我有赌债，
I can't pay.
我付不起钱。
They can kill me.
他们可以杀了我。
I beg you.
我求求你。
I beg you, I was wrong
求求你了，我错了
don't kill me.
别杀我。
where is he
他在哪里
Old factory.
老工厂。
Is it in the old factory?
是在老工厂吗？
Take me to find him.
带我去找他。
I will take you away.
我会带你走。
I took you to find him.
我带你去找他。
He is waiting for me.
他正在等我。
You can kill him,
你可以杀了他，
if you dare play tricks again,
如果你还敢再搞恶作剧
I will shoot you dead.
我会开枪打死你。
He's in the old factory in front of it
他在前面的旧工厂里
wait for me on the second floor.
在二楼等我。
do not forget
不要忘记
The muzzle of my gun is behind you
我的枪口在你身后
understand?
理解？
He is very alert,
他非常警觉，
I'll go calm him down first.
我先去安抚他一下。
Don't mess around.
别乱来。
Xiao Tao.
Xiao Tao.
I've been found out!
我被发现了！
Shi Yang is now outside.
石洋现在就在外面。
Inside the pendant there is no information.
吊坠内部没有任何信息。
He lied to me
他对我撒谎
I came to tell you
我是来告诉你的
there are still other clues that can find it.
还有其他线索可以找到它。
Shi Yang has heart disease?
石洋有心脏病吗？
Every Thursday
每个星期四
going to Ci'an hospital to look for a doctor
去慈安医院找医生
to take a drug called nitroglycerin.
服用一种叫做硝酸甘油的药物。
Ci'an Hospital.
慈安医院。
You go quickly.
你快点走吧。
Hurry up.
赶快。
So what about you?
那么你呢？
Do not mind me.
别管我。
I think it's for my sister's sake.
我想这是为了姐姐的缘故。
But I can't leave you.
但我不能离开你。
Don't worry, he won't do anything to me
放心，他不会对我做什么
you go quickly, you go quickly!
你快点走，你快点走！
Bitch woman!
贱女人！
Betray me!
背叛我！
Go away!
离开！
Die!
死！
If one day you go to war,
如果有一天你去打仗，
would you be willing to give your life for your sister?
你愿意为你的妹妹付出生命吗？
Dad is home.
爸爸回家了。
My son.
我的儿子。
Ayah.
呀呀。
Obedient or not?
听话还是不听话？
Good son.
好儿子。
Ayah.
呀呀。
Why did you come home so late?
你怎么这么晚才回家？
Dad has a lot to do
爸爸还有很多事要做
So why haven't you slept yet?
那你怎么还没睡呢？
He says
他说
have to wait for you to come back to tell the tale
必须等你回来才能讲故事
he just slept
他刚刚睡着了
Good.
好的。
Dad will tell you a story.
爸爸会给你讲一个故事。
What do you want to hear?
你想听什么？
About tin soldiers?
关于锡兵？
That...
那...
Persistent soldier.
坚持不懈的战士。
Those little soldiers, right?
那些小战士吧？
Correct.
正确的。
Dad will tell you.
爸爸会告诉你的。
Once upon a time,
曾几何时，
there was a soldier
有一个士兵
he always carried a gun on his shoulder.
他肩上总是扛着一把枪。
Bold and cool.
大胆又酷。
Dad, someday I will also hold a gun.
爸爸，有一天我也会拿着枪。
Good.
好的。
Our future fans
我们未来的粉丝
also carries a Maoser pistol on his shoulder.
肩上还扛着一把毛瑟手枪。
Bold and cool.
大胆又酷。
On the table.
在桌子上。
There are lots of other toys.
还有很多其他玩具。
There is a beautiful paper dancer
有一个美丽的纸舞者
he wears a
他穿着
a beautiful rose brooch.
美丽的玫瑰胸针。
This little soldier really likes it.
这个小战士真的很喜欢。
Every day looking at him,
每天看着他，
dream one day
有一天做梦
to be his bride.
成为他的新娘。
However, there is a little monster.
然而，有一个小怪物。
Deeply hates Xiao Xi's army.
深深憎恨小夕的军队。
As long as he's not focused
只要他不专心
threw it into the furnace
把它扔进炉子里
is Xiao Xi Bing sick?
小西冰有病吗？
Of course it hurts.
当然很痛。
But Xiao Xi's soldiers were very brave.
但萧熙的士兵却非常勇敢。
Even though the flames had engulfed his body,
尽管火焰已经吞噬了他的身体，
and melted his body slowly,
并慢慢融化他的身体，
however, he remained strong.
然而，他仍然坚强。
With force.
用武力。
At this time,
此时，
suddenly there was a strong wind.
突然刮起了大风。
through the wind,
透过风，
the beautiful dancer flies.
美丽的舞者飞翔。
Fly, fly
飞啊飞啊
terbang ke samping Xiao Xijin.
terbang ke samping Xiao Xijin.
Sister!
姐姐！
Sis.
姐姐。
Look at it.
看它。
Lu seemed to be saying something.
卢似乎在说什么。
Come on, listen.
来吧，听着。
Harder.
更难。
Abandoned by the dancer.
被舞者抛弃。
Rose brooch.
玫瑰胸针。
What's that?
那是什么？
What rose brooch?
什么玫瑰胸针？
Maybe it's important information.
也许这是重要的信息。
Finally he confessed.
最后他承认了。
Listen again.
再听一遍。
From now on
今后
them
他们
will be together forever.
将永远在一起。
What's together again?
怎么又在一起了？
Which other communist members were you with?
您和其他哪些共产党员在一起？
Say.
说。
What is your online account?
您的在线帐户是什么？
Say it.
说吧。
Is dead.
死了。
Just opened your mouth
刚刚张开嘴
didn't say anything already died.
什么也没说就已经死了。
Go away
离开
everyone will die.
每个人都会死。
Die according to the desired state
根据想要的状态模具
That's appropriate.
那是合适的。
Keep your hands away.
把你的手拿开。
Leopard sellers eat together
豹子卖家一起吃饭
hold on, hold on
坚持住，坚持住
keep your hands away
把你的手拿开
everyone stand still, don't move!
大家都站稳，别动！
Grand Princess.
大公主。
Look at that person,
看看那个人，
look familiar?
看起来熟悉？
You look it
你看看
a little nervous.
一点紧张。
Look at it.
看它。
The money is gone.
钱没了。
Going home I couldn't explain to my wife and children.
回家后我无法向妻子和孩子解释。
Like...
喜欢...
Where have you met?
你们在哪里见过？
I've remembered.
我记住了。
That day at the Divine Hai Sect's Tea House,
当日海神宗茶楼，
he was one of the tea guests in the private room on the second floor.
他是二楼包间的茶客之一。
Correct.
正确的。
However, at that time I did not suspect them.
不过，当时我并没有怀疑他们。
Then let it all go.
然后就让一切过去吧。
The person the military police are looking for is definitely him.
军警要找的人肯定是他。
If not,
如果不，
shall we report him?
我们要举报他吗？
You can still make a contribution.
您仍然可以做出贡献。
Pig brains.
猪脑。
If this person is taken away by the military police,
如果这个人被宪兵带走的话
are we still doing great?
我们还做得很好吗？
So how?
又怎样？
Tuan Zhang
Tuan Zhang
lucky today too.
今天也很幸运。
Fortunately.
幸运的是。
You still say you can't play.
你还说你不会玩。
Next time together
下次一起
Ping family
平家
I can't sleep.
我睡不着。
Can't you sleep either?
你也睡不着吗？
Can you dance?
你能跳舞吗？
It's like we never danced.
就好像我们从来没有跳舞一样。
According to you,
照你说的，
what is moonlight?
什么是月光？
Untouched.
未受影响。
Also untouched.
也未曾动过。
So...
所以...
His presence
他的存在
like a lot of big things
喜欢很多大事
the eternal.
永恒的。
Even though he disappeared,
尽管他消失了，
but he was still there.
但他还在那里。
I can feel
我可以感觉到
today you are very sad.
今天你很伤心。
Is it true?
这是真的吗？
It means
它的意思是
you're sad too.
你也很难过。
Today we don't fight anymore.
今天我们不再吵架了。
Accompany me like this, how about it?
就这样陪着我，怎么样？
Okay
好的
section chief Chen
陈科长
Did you go to work early today?
今天你上班早吗？
Where's the newspaper?
报纸在哪儿？
Has it arrived?
到了吗？
It's arrived, it's done.
已经到了，已经完成了。
Here.
这里。
Your new declaration and newspaper.
你的新宣言和报纸。
Good.
好的。
Thank You.
谢谢。
No need to hesitate.
无需犹豫。
The act of printing fake money is called Project Shan.
印假钱的行为被称为“山计划”。
Hear - hear other than money
听到-听到除了钱之外的声音
the Japanese are still trying to fake it
日本人仍在试图伪造它
coins issued in parts of the CCP border
中共边境部分地区发行的硬币
there are two military spies hiding in Yan'an
延安藏有两名军事间谍
took away copper coins,
拿走了铜币，
and printing paper
和打印纸
xi Que is the general of the army.
西缺是大将军。
Liuli Guoguo often went to the dance hall these two days.
琉璃果果这两天经常去舞厅。
What is related to this problem?
与这个问题有什么关系？
Didn't ask me recently if it happened
最近没有问我是否发生过
cases related to dance halls
与舞厅相关的案例
I actually remember it
我其实还记得
two days ago there was a murder case.
两天前，发生了一起谋杀案。
The deceased was a female dancer.
死者是一名女舞者。
Where did the incident occur?
事件发生在哪里？
In an abandoned factory
在一座废弃的工厂里
the victim was named Cai Hongling
受害人名叫蔡红玲
female dancers in the Xianle ballroom
仙乐舞厅的女舞者
the cause of death was
死亡原因是
shot.
射击。
Shot three times
射了三枪
and fell from the 2nd floor
然后从二楼掉下来
Immediately died on the spot.
当场死亡。
This man.
这个男人。
Has this man been found?
这个人找到了吗？
Not yet.
还没有。
He had indeed seen it
他确实见过
traces of a man's life in his house.
一个人在他的房子里生活的痕迹。
But after asking people around,
但询问了周围的人后，
they all said that he didn't know what this man was
他们都说他不知道这个人是什么
is it true that this man lives in his house?
这个人真的住在他的房子里吗？
No wonder Guoguo wanted to go to the dance hall these two days.
难怪果果这两天想去舞厅。
It turns out he wanted to approach Xi Que through Cai Hongling.
原来他想通过蔡红绫接近西缺。
But why do you want to look?
但你为什么想看？
their own people?
他们自己的人？
Why so much interest in this case?
为什么对这个案例如此感兴趣？
I suspect,
我猜测，
This case is related to my wife.
这个案子和我的妻子有关。
Your wife.
你妻子。
Having a relationship with a female dancer?
与女舞者发生关系？
The last few nights were so sad,
前几晚的心情真的很悲伤
what Cai Hongling was killed
蔡洪龄被杀的事
Cai Hongling to help him?
蔡红菱要帮他？
Maybe Liuli Guoguo knows the whereabouts of magpie.
也许琉璃果果知道喜鹊的下落。
That way you can get through
这样你就可以通过
to find it.
找到它。
Why frown?
为何皱眉？
What's wrong with your wife?
你老婆怎么了？
Maybe he has changed his mind?
也许他改变了主意？
I shouldn't have given away the green sofa that time.
那次我不应该把绿色沙发送人。
Go back to your car.
回到你的车上。
Getting married is not easy.
结婚并不容易。
Go!
去！
Staying single is better.
保持单身更好。
Second floor balcony.
二楼阳台。
I put a pot of yellow chrysanthemums,
我放了一盆黄菊花，
is a safe signal.
是一个安全信号。
You changed Huang Ju to Zi Ju,
You changed Huang Ju to Zi Ju,
indicates something has happened.
表明发生了某事。
I've obviously changed Huang Ju to Zi Ju.
我明明已经把黄菊改成子菊了。
Who put Huang Ju back?
谁把黄菊放回去了？
What is it?
它是什么？
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I...
我...
Come buy things.
快来买东西吧。
Purchase of goods?
购买商品？
This shop is closed.
这家店关门了。
Isn't it still open?
不是还开着吗？
Wait a minute
等一下
the boss of this restaurant, Boss Lu.
这家餐厅的老板，陆老板。
He is a member of the CCP
他是中共党员
has been arrested.
已被捕。
Understand?
理解？
Is there anyone?
有人吗?
There are definitely people who want to impersonate old people
肯定有人想冒充老人
ambush here.
埋伏在这里。
We still don't know the comrades who died on the old road.
那些死在老路上的战友我们仍然不认识。
But how could this person know
但这人怎么会知道
security connection secret code?
安全连接密码？
Are you a new doctor?
你是新医生吗？
Your lipstick color is very nice.
你的口红颜色很好看。
Buy where?
哪里买？
When there is a discount at Yong'an Mall.
永安商城有折扣的时候。
I feel like the colors are too flashy.
我感觉颜色太花哨了。
How could it be
怎么会这样
very suitable for your skin color
非常适合你的肤色
Is that true?
真的吗？
Correct
正确的
The aspirin you want is in locker number five
你想要的阿司匹林在五号储物柜里
Thank You
谢谢
get you a medicine bag.
给你一个药袋。
Thank You.
谢谢。
Take it.
拿去。
Just sign here.
只需在这里签名即可。
I also want to buy lipstick.
我也想买口红。
Two days later, we went to the mall together.
两天后，我们一起去了商场。
Good.
好的。
You have really good taste.
你的品味真不错。
Later, help me with suggestions.
稍后再帮我提建议。
You are so Beautiful
你真美
whatever you wear, it's still beautiful.
不管你穿什么，它仍然很漂亮。
Signed.
签。
Good.
好的。
Until found.
直到被发现。
Miss, wait a moment.
小姐，请稍等。
What is it?
它是什么？
Nona,
诺娜，
your scarf fell.
你的围巾掉下来了。
Thank You.
谢谢。
Is there any clue about the magpie at Ci'an Hospital?
慈安医院的喜鹊有什么线索吗？
Who is that doctor?
那个医生是谁？
Road.
路。
Ping Family
平家
luFang
luFang
Long time no see
好久不见
I've been transferred
我已被转移
to the document room of the planning section of the military police headquarters.
到宪兵总部规划科文件室。
It's been very busy lately.
最近很忙。
Can't let go.
不能放手。
That is an important department.
这是一个重要的部门。
What important position?
什么重要地位？
Out of the blue...
出乎意料的是...
Because I can speak a little Japanese,
因为我会说一点日语，
making me have to run on both sides of the Gendarmerie Commander and Shangxing.
害得我不得不在宪兵司令和尚兴的两边跑。
Very tiring.
很累。
How about you?
你呢？
Came here to work.
来这里工作。
Do you know these people
你认识这些人吗
is what person?
是什么人？
Member of the Chinese Communist Party.
中国共产党党员。
these two days,
这两天，
military police have arrested many people,
军警逮捕了很多人
So,
所以，
how long are they detained?
他们被拘留多久？
I heard he's going to be sent to detention,
听说他要被拘留了
probably won't come back.
可能不会回来。
Very scary.
很吓人。
That...
那...
Working for the Japanese,
为日本人工作，
have to be more careful.
必须更加小心。
You too.
你也是。
Then I'll go in first.
那我就先进去了。
Sir, is it finished?
先生，完结了吗？
Thank You.
谢谢。
Okay.
好的。
You work first.
你先工作。
Back to chatting.
回到聊天。
Until found.
直到被发现。
Luo Guanqun had already grasped the old path.
罗冠群已经掌握了老路。
You've captured Jin Ming.
你抓住了金明。
You've been very accomplished lately.
你最近很有成就。
Lu, it was Luo Guan Qun who snatched my services.
卢，是罗冠群抢走了我的服务。
He... He's outrageous.
他……他太无耻了。
Luo Guan Qun has the ability.
罗冠群有能力。
You have your abilities.
你有你的能力。
My greatest ability
我最大的能力
is loyal to Village Chief Mu.
对穆村长忠诚。
Your greatest ability
你最大的能力
is telling you to feed the horse
告诉你去喂马
or feeding pigs,
或喂猪，
you can even close
你甚至可以关闭
very strictly.
非常严格。
Luo Guanqun couldn't even put a finger in.
罗冠群一根手指头都插不进去。
I'm guarding your house.
我守护着你的家。
Shan's project goes smoothly.
单的项目进展顺利。
Now the scale is getting bigger.
现在规模越来越大了。
Now the problem is,
现在的问题是，
lack of money.
缺钱。
Your previous fundraising plans,
您之前的筹款计划，
even though it is not used
即使没有使用
but I'm always optimistic.
但我总是很乐观。
Mu Village Chief,
穆村村长，
I promise,
我保证，
as long as it goes according to my plan,
只要按照我的计划进行
will definitely give Shan project
一定会给Shan项目
money that Shan Jihua would never use up.
单季华永远用不完的钱。
Trust me.
相信我。
Here.
这里。
Mu Village Chief,
穆村村长，
I recently understood a logic.
我最近明白了一个逻辑。
What principle?
什么原则？
It's actually this guy
原来是这个人
and horses are the same thing.
和马是同一个东西。
What a good horse.
多好的一匹马啊。
Her skin can be seen from afar,
远远就能看到她的皮肤，
take a closer look at the feet and hands
仔细看看脚和手
front view wide chest,
正面看胸宽，
the back looks like a butt.
背面看起来像屁股。
Look at it.
看它。
Do I look like Shinixuan Takeda?
我像武田新轩吗？
Good.
好的。
You...
你...
Truly a genius
真是个天才
Pagi, Qian Xiu Cai
Pagi, Qian Xiu Cai
morning section chief Chen
陈晨科长
where is the newspaper?
报纸在哪里？
Have arrived.
已经到了。
Your new declaration and newspaper.
你的新宣言和报纸。
Good.
好的。
Section Chief Chen
陈科长
I remember you first
我首先记得你
don't like seeing new announcements,
不喜欢看到新的公告，
I also often forget it at my place.
我也经常把它忘在我的地方。
This is because in this latest announcement
这是因为在最新的公告中
created the Wang Du Lu martial arts novel series
创作《望独路》武侠小说系列
kun Lun who was surprised
惊讶的昆仑
I feel addicted.
我感觉上瘾了。
Then, next time I'd like to see it too.
那么，下次我也想去看看。
Don't you look at your Eastern Zhou country records anymore?
你不再看你们东周国的记录了吗？
However, how do you see it?
然而，你怎么看呢？
All these pages?
所有这些页面？
I am
我是
most like the story plagiarism save to save Zhao.
最喜欢抄袭救救赵的故事。
You mean Ying, the high noble of Wei country, right?
你是说魏国的大贵族嬴吧？
Truly.
确实。
That person, Ying,
那人，莹，
he used to be
他以前是
is a guardian
是监护人
same as me.
跟我一样。
But then
但是之后
even became one of the four young masters of the warring country.
甚至成为了战国四少爷之一。
From all corners of this country.
来自这个国家的各个角落。
Unexpected
意外
Qian Xiu also had the same ambition
千修也有同样的抱负
I have a nightmare
我做了一个噩梦
I'm just blind.
我只是瞎了而已。
Good.
好的。
Go ahead.
前进。
Director Ding.
丁主任.
I'll just go home alone.
我就一个人回家吧。
Can't.
不能。
Master Shan Xia specifically ordered
山下大师特意吩咐
must get you home safely
必须让你安全回家
Okay.
好的。
Didn't the lights just come on?
灯不是刚亮吗？
Why is it dead now?
怎么现在死了？